non-human,
and today is the fifty-second,
Here we go.
and it's pretty quiet here,
right?
very safe.
then I pulled breakfast
for me.
that there,
if we have a room with a bathroom outside,
you know,
from a thousand,
sixteen hundred,
one thousand six hundred.
this value is not included either,
nor bed linen.
and then if suddenly no more money comes in,
How do you do it?
then you have to make a right investment,
slowly,
leaves every time so you're making fun of these things,
understand?
I need to do 1 financial planning.
I'll show you my financial plan here.
connects.
so here I am separating my personal account
of the company.
bro,
what's that going to be like?
I saved two thousand reais a month for me to pay
rent.
I'm calculating more or less an average of seven hundred
real,
then a kitnet,
I don't know, a room.
I will put the limitation here,
about a thousand reais per month,
about one hundred and fifty reais of hygiene,
one hundred and fifty reais
from others
that would be others,
Internet,
washing,
these things.
I'm at the gas station,
so i have it very easy
so use the internet from the gas station
laundry.
now i don't know, bro,
so i need
Guarantee me.
it's on.
now come here
what I'm considering.
company,
connects.
all this I will put in the company
so that
emergency reserve
invest in truffles,
or chevas,
I use it to be able to deliver.
the truffles,
logistics,
customer service puts gasoline
then you arrive,
today is mine
my work locomotive
then company
I need money
to set up a business,
I sent two thousand reais into another account
and my Cora bank account
will only stay with my company
to make it easier i
sort things out in order to put together a business plan.
Cayão what is the business you are going to set up
now that you have money?
brother I have some ideas,
but I confess to you that I'm a little confused,
I'm looking for a place to stay,
I'm packing horses
and at the same time
separating things.
guy if you have any idea of business there
to be able to give me 1 light
send in the comments that really bro
I'm in need of this a lot.
great day for you there bro
and remember to thank
but do not remain is us,
Can the crowd understand that they have to separate?
a kiss in Me.